RABIN PUN

WEB DEVELOPER

CONTACT

rabin.pun88@gmail.com rabinpun.co.uk linkedin.com/in/rabin-pun 07861496621 Reading

EDUCATION

Msc Computer Science

University of Birmingham, UK Sept 2018 - Sept 2019 Grade: Merit (67.5%)

Bsc Nutrition

Oxford Brookes University, UK Sept 2011 - Jun 2014 Grade: Upper Second Class

A-Levels

Reading College, Reading Sept 2008 - Jun 2010

SKILLS

- JavaScript
- Typescript
- · HTML5/CSS
- React.js / Node.js / AWS
- Material UI/ Formik
- React Query
- MYSQL/Oracle/PostgreSQL
- · GitHub/Bamboo CI/CD
- Salesforce

CERTIFICATION

Microsoft Azure Fundamentals

PROFILE

Technically competent and result-oriented with over 3 years of experience in web development using React and Node. Migrated legacy web portals into modern tech stacks that reduced the technical debt. Always keen to learn modern tech frameworks and problem solving techniques. Currently, seeking for a mid-level developer role in a fast-paced tech company that offers a good career progression.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Junior Web Developer

Keyloop, Reading

Jan 2021 - Present

- Migrating legacy web portals into new portals using React, Typescript and Node
- Working on frontend and backend development with the best coding practices.
- Implementing new features according to the business needs.
- Collaborate with third party provider teams and integrating their product into our project.
- Liaise with UI/UX team in improving the user experience and customer satisfaction that ultimately helps to build a user friendly web applications.
- Taking responsibility and be the technical point of contact in the absence of other team members.
- Providing continuous technical support to support team in resolving any issues related to customer web portals.
- Attend meeting regularly in order to track the progress of the project.

Graduate Software Engineer

Dec 2019 - Nov 2020

Tata Consultancy Services (TCS)

 Exposure with client and server side scripting in JavaScript and ServiceNow APIs.

Microbiology Analyst

Mar 2016 - Sept 2018

Thames Water, Reading

AWARDS

- £100 gift voucher from Keyloop in recognition of hard work on successfully re-branding of the company.
- "Take ownership" award of £25 gift voucher from Thames Water for dealing professionally with samples and associated courier disruptions on weekends.